崂诉在^m  洛杉已高_109A氏度
The heat wave continues. it's 109 degrees in los angeles.
洛杉受干旱之苦
As drought-ridden los angeles
高厥谷涫苷勰
swelters in agonising heat,...
而街^的毒品稽查也在如火如荼的M行
..drug lords wage warfare in the streets.
又一次公_抗在...
Yet another open conflict...
天哪  快我x_@
oh, fuck this! get me out of here!
有擅T警在火拼中受重
Two motorcycle officers horribly wounded in a crossfire,...
警方似乎o力解救他
The police seemingly unable to rescue them
多次英勇的突都]有成功
in spite of several desperate,heroic attempts.
@里已完全失去控制
It's completely out of control down here.
我辛苦I的酒吧全]了
My beautiful cantina, everything I own,
什么都被打碎了
they shot it to pieces.
我的微波t  自诱翦  烤箱
My microwave, my automatic steamer, my grill...
你@群混蛋
You fucking pendejos!
去你他的
Fuck you!
我是托尼・普波  @里是核心F龉目
Tony pope, live with hard core
槟做F蟮
on the scene andin yourface.
@里就像但丁描的地z
It's like dante's hell.
硝  和y以忍受的高...
Smoke, fire, oppressive heat,...
哥比和牙I加的大鬼
As colombian and jamaican drug fiends
再次把洛杉成了屠宰
Again transform LA into a slaughterhouse.
@里到底lf了算  警察  非也
Who the hell's in charge down here? the cops?Uh-uh
他是人当多  b渚良的笨蛋
They're outmanned, outgunned and incompetent.
在塔霍湖家中度假的市L先生
Mr mayor, on vacation in your home in lake tahoe,...
快把^放下  s快到@眍C布戒懒
..get off your butt, get down here and declare martial law!
e我心神不  丹尼
Ok, don't keep me in suspense, danny boy!
今天真不太平
It has not been a nice day!
奢v摩托倒在卡那
Two motors pulled over a truck，
好踝×酥虚g毒警的
Stumbled right in the middle of a narc stakeout.
十全副武b的哥比
You know, ten colombians and scorpios
人就足以Ω段
armed to fuck all.
他想回老巢
They're trying to get in their headquarters.
我得阻止他
We're keeping them pinned down.
不^那些警察就快因出血^多而死了
but those officers are bleeding to death.
他快不行了  警官
Fuck! they're dying, man.
他的重武器在哪
Where the hell is special weapons?
它在圣佩德_和牙I加人交火
They're still tied up in that shootout in san pedro with the jamaicans.
他袈淞艘患苤鄙C
They shot down a chopper.
米斯和詹森快不住了
Mills and Johnson won't last much longer.
我需要一vb甲去救他
We need an assault vehicle to go get 'em.
好吧  我硐胂朕k法
I'm gonna chat with these assholes.
-看我信  o我火力掩o  -明白
- When I give the signal, give me some cover! - Got it!
@也太小了
Too small.
就@影
Right.
快c  快c
Come on! come on!
快他x_@
Get 'em out of here! now!
戆
Vamonos!
幼骺禳c
Get 'em out! get 'em out!
-戆  -戆
- Vamonos! - Vamonos!
你@些狗sN
Hey, assholes!
~克  你]事吧
Mike, are you ok?
]事  快去抓那些余孽
yeah. let's get the rest.
不行  海{曼指]官有命令
we can't. orders from chief heinemann.
我原地待命
He says surround building and wait.
-待什么命  -我怎么知道
- Wait for what? - I don't know!
也S是特N部  邦探T  毒品管制局
Some bullshit special unit. the feds, the dea.
如果等那图一聿迨
If we let those bastards get dug in now
我得⑦@座房子夷槠降夭拍茏プ∷
we'll have to level the building to get them out
-狗娘B的  -]e
- Hijo de puta. - No, es para mi.
戆  行影
Vamonos!vamonos!
s快戆
Venga!aprisa!
戆
Venga!
我浜昧  戆
Come and get it. ei scorpio is ready.
-警官  上面有你的人  -]有
- Sarge, any of your people in the building? - No.
行
Let's go.
中尉  你不能M去  海{曼R上就到
Lieutenant, can't let you in. Heinemann's on his way.
他去死吧  幼骺禳c
Heinemann can kiss my sweet ass! come on!
死的  跟上他
Goddamn it. go with him.
三  二  一
Three, two, one...
行
Go!
出去  退后
Get back, back, back. back.
隔壁也z查完
Next door over.
在T口守著
Take this room!
我在二  有人受  求支援
First floor, officer down. we need backup.
e
Freeze!
我fe
I said hold it!
把放下
Now, lay your guns down.
是走下磉是跳下去S你便
you can walk down or fly, it's your choice.
但先把放下  混蛋
I said put it down, asshole!
不
No!
^去看看
let's do it now!
放松
Take it easy.
真他
Damn, it's hot.
肯定是眼花了
Must be losing it.
~克
Mike!
散_  搜查整屋
Spread out. secure the roof.
]事了  我在@
Just take it easy. I'm righthere.
警蠼獬  一切正常
All clear. all clear on the site.
丹尼
Oh, dannyboy.
我得下去了
I gotta get down from here.
天哪
Shit.
全面搜查  哪佣疾灰放^
Ok, search the roof. check every floor.
也S有余h
maybe someone else...
把@里封i起  不S任何人x_
Seal it off. no one leaves.
丹尼  快我x_@鬼地方
Danny, get me off this damn roof.
-找到他的同h了  -有人捷足先登了
- You get the rest of them? - Somebody beat us to it.
利昂娜
Leona.
我的天哪
Oh, shit.
@喊l生了什么
what happened to ei scorpio?
他正在吃午餐
He's out front having lunch.
@究竟是怎么回事
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
他都身首
They've been cut to pieces.
肯定是牙I加人
must be the jamaicans.
像他的L格  但他去哪毫四
their style, but where the hell did they go?
法t硪郧  不嗜魏稳诉M@里
Ok, nobody gets in here until forensic arrives. nobody.
你知道程序的
Ok, you know the drill.
~克  你看上面
Mike. Up there.
他肯定是在@罕  然后有人...
He must have been killed out here, and then someone...
起a有35到40英尺高  ]有K子和梯子
That's about 35, 40 feet. no rope, no ladder.
@家伙有190到195磅
The guy weighs about 190, 195 pounds.
你肯定不能把他煸谀
You couldn't carry him up there.
中尉
Lieutenant?
副指]官海{曼在窍
Deputy chief heinemann's downstairs.
他要你和你的人s快x_@
he wants you and your people out of the building now.
@混蛋
Ah, son of a bitch.
到底l生了什么事
What the fuck is going on?
@不是好兆^  ~克  一c都不好
This is not good, mike. not good at all.
-查查@家伙的底  -我的
- I want a real name on this joker, ok?  - You got it.
~克
Mike.
菲  你怎么也在@
Phil, this is quite a surprise.
什么L把你吹砹
what brings you down from the palace?
~克  你我很失望  我F在很不高d
You let me down, mike. you're making me look bad.
我以槲已_成共R
I thought we had an understanding.
我MM心思你到@
I put my ass on the line to get you here,...
只希望你能合作一c
..and all I expect is a little cooperation!
我告V^你@是邦{查局的案子
You were told this was a federal matter.
你最好e插手  你竟然`抗命令
Yet you disobeyed an order to stay out of the building.
e@诱f  菲  是我淼
Don't let this get out, phil, but it's a fucking war down here.
兵就要服拿令  e找借口
Soldiers take orders. don't push it!
菲  我]有找借口
I'll push it as far as I can, phil
你在市^k公室里DUP的r候
cos we're fighting for our lives here,...
我在@好八鸲
..while you're downtown pushing pencils and kissing ass!
我不任何人的  特e是邦{查局
I don't roll over for anybody, especially the feds,...
除非o我一好的解
..without a goddamn good explanation!
把@些x器搬去三
Take this equipment up to the third floor.
_始行
come on, let's move!
-走吧  -Σ黄  L官
- Let's go. - Excuse me, sir!
海{曼  他到底在干什么
What the hell is going on here, heinemann?
不指]
Insubordination.
不服纳霞IУ拿令
disregard for direct orders from a supervising officer.
L回你阿瓦拉多的C吧
Now get back to your cage at alvarado.
-我你RR什么是不指]  你...  -e
- I'll show you insubordination, you son of... - No, no, no!
你跑什么  有N^
Where you running to? come here!
]必要@  ~克  何必呢
You don't need this, mike. it's not worth it.
放松一c
Relax.
真他的
Oh, fuck!
我槟碜钚蟮
I have an update for you.
@次交火  五名哥比毒
In a shootout, five members of one colombian drug gang...
被他的κ⒑
..were ambushed by their bloody rivals,
牙I加的伏都教徒神秘失
the jamaican voodoo posse, who escaped withouta trace
再次愚弄了...
again making total fools of...
-有位警官想你  -在那后面
- A detective is here to see you. - Back there.
著  女士  你家所漏水
Listen, lady, you got a backed-up toilet.
需要的是水管工而不是警察
Call a plumber, not the cops.
你的陶者^期了
This licence has expired.
胡扯  我六月前付^X了
Bullshit! I paid that fee six months ago.
-小心我揍你  -坐下 s快
- I'll kick your ass! - Sit down! right now!
-走  快走  -你他冷oc
- Move! get your ass movin'! - Just calm the fuck down!
你在看什么
What you lookin' at?
你要做的就是
And all you got to do...
把球放在球座上  然后]U
..is tee it high and let it fly.
完美的]U
Ow! dead solid perfect.
你要住
Now, remember
你要看好距x  oo地抓住球U
for distance you gotta gently but firmly grip the club.
哈里根中尉  我是探Tm伯特  防l司的
Lieutenant harrigan! detective lambert, rampart division.
小伙子  先坐一  我一找你
Hey, kid, just have a seat. I'll be right with you.
-嘿  ^  -你先ef  ~克
- Hey, cap. - Don't start, mike.
海{曼已警告我
Heinemann's already been up my ass so
我小心我^上的跫帽
Far I won't be able to sit down for a week.
我A不了他
We're not winning this war.
不管你愿不愿意  有些事你必要做
As much as it'll piss you off, you'll have to play the game.
而且必立即去做
"effective immediately,
邦特遣人彼得・P斯
A federal task force under special agent peter keyes...
{查一系列犯罪活
Will investigate criminal activities
包括一些受限案件
Involving the trafficking of controlled substances."
你要全力配合他
And you will extend him your full cooperation.
你是要我把案子交o他
So you're cutting off my dick and shoving it up my ass.
邦{查局是老大  我得它的
The feds are calling the shots on this. my hands are tied!
-什么事  -皮格瑞姆上尉  我是彼得・P斯
- Peah? - Captain pilgrim, peter keyes.
-很高d到你  -我也是  L官
- It's good to meet you. - And you, sir.
~克・哈里根中尉
Lieutenant mike harrigan.
邦{查局探T彼得・P斯
special agent peter keyes, dea.
久仰大名
Heard a lot about you.
很抱歉  @是司法程序
I'm sorry for this jurisdictional intrusion.
不是f我比你嗔Υ
Don't mean to be stepping on your toes.
我只是想P除金・威利的伏都教
But we want to prevent king willie's voodoo
他控制了整西海岸
Gangs from taking over the entire west coast.
我想多透露一些o你
I wish I could tell you more.
但@可娴揭恍┖诵}
But we have a large number of deep-cover operatives involved.
你知道的  我都有各自的
You know how it is. we all have a job to do.
F在  我保C
Now, I'm sure
我尊重彼此并各司其
we can respect each other's situation and act responsibly.
合作是我突出的性
Well,...um, cooperation...is my middle name.
一
I'll see you around.
我{^  我叫吉瑞・m伯特
I'm the new transfer, jerry lambert.
我f  你先坐一
Like I said, have a seat.
一找你
I'll be right with you.
-@公子哥是l  -一笨蛋
- Who is this dude? - Yeah, what an asshole.
丹尼  查到什么了
All right, danny boy, what we got?
查到什么?
What have we got?
里面是五v不明人
five lowlife scorpions make it into the building.
然后  他成了烤肉串
The next minute... they're all shish kebab.
]有
Not one bullet wound.
不是榱硕酒泛湾X  因檫@些|西撒了一地
It wasn't drugs or money. there's a shit load of that.
也S金・威利雇了某害角色
Maybe king willie brought in some outside talent.
他正@示他的本事
He's making his big move.
他在我上去之前已解Q了鸲
A pro would have split the moment he heard us.
不止⒘艘人  也S我到他了
More than one, we would have seen them.
究竟是l在最后r刻
Whoever did this waited until the last minute,...
⑺手持C的
..and then took out four men
悍匪yy放倒
armed with machine guns by hand!
然后在我眼皮底下溜走了呢
And then got by us.
也S我雇蛩
let's put him on the payroll.Maybe we should give him a job.
我和我搭n守在翘萆r
So me and my partner bolt up the stairs,
有人大叫血腥\
Somebody is screaming bloody murder...
-你我f  -什么
- You gotta... you gotta hear this. - What?!
嘿  忘了告V你
Hey. hey, I forgot to tell you.
看那家伙了
See that guy there?
他接菲利斯的班
That's ferris's replacement.
他叫吉瑞・m伯特
This guy's jerry lambert.
是防l司的行b
the lone ranger from rampart station.
有他那拥莫行b
That's the lone ranger?
我以樗是磉@盒蘅照{的
I thought he was here to fix the air conditioning.
我就f"女士你被捕了"  她f"槭裁"
I said "lady, you are under arrest." and she said "why?"
我f"因槟⑺懒四阏煞"
I said "because your husband is dead. you killed him."
-你知道她f什么  -不知道
- You know what she said, didn't miss a beat? - uh, no.
她f"我以前常常@么刺@混蛋
She said "i stabbed that son of a bitch plenty of times.
可他都]死啊"
He never died on me before."
他好像在挑逗利昂娜
Looks like he's putting the moves to leona.
他犯的第一大e`
His first big mistake.
我f^你
I have heard about you.
-真的  -]e
- Yeah? - Yeah!
-比如你上搭n被  -什么
- Like your last partner got shot. - What?
e老p著我  笨蛋
You try that cowboy shit with me, fucker,...
要不然我把你了
..you can kiss these goodbye.
-明白了  -明白了
- Got it? - Yeah, I got it. unhh!
我想你已^三位了
Well, well, I see that the three of you have met.
m伯特  如果你忍得住
Lambert, if you're feeling up to it,...
可以慢慢地走到中尉那
..why don't you limp your way in to the lieutenant.
他想和你
He wants to talk to you.
好的
Yeah.
-你真是呐孩  -我喜g@
- You're a bad girl. - Ooh, I like that.
不  不  不
No, no, no!
天哪  @女人是不是碓陆了
Goddamn, is that bitch on the rag or what?
小伙子  接下砦宜f的就是所^的"矩"
This is what I call "the speech", kid.
我只f一次  注意
I only give it once, so pay attention.
到目前橹  都是些小打小[的游
Until now, it's all been fun and games, cops and robbers,
有油炸圈
Dunking doughnuts.
但F在不一恿  我得告V你@是^
But you're in the shit now. metro command is a war zone.
中尉  我明白
Lieutenant, I've paid my dues.
我M了很多功夫才{到@
I had to bust my ass to get my transfer.
@我很吃@  小伙子
And that scares the shit out of me, kid.
]人要求到@
No one requests to come here
除非他想P名立f
unless they want a reputation.
@里]有地方人表F自己
There's no room for anyone looking to prove themselves.
我也^不允S@
I won't stand for it.
e我不高d
Don't get me wrong.
我需要好警察
We need good cops
他f你很棒
and they say you're good at what you do.
但是F精神是第一位的
But the team comes first.
以F橹  才是重要的
You live by that, and you'll be ok.
我在等著你
and we'll all be there for you.
住  凡事都有擅
Remember, the door swings both ways.
就@些
That's it.
嘿  小伙子
Hey, kid.
g迎加入鸲
Welcome to the war.
小子  是不是做的太^火了
Ok, guys. this has gone too far now, huh?
著  小子
Hey, hey, guys.
我知道你想恐我
I-l-l know you're trying to scare me, huh?
你做的很好
Well, you did a pretty good job, man.
我F在很害怕
I'm scared now.
e@
Stop it now.
我o你X
I can pay you.
砂偃fFn  R上就o
$2 million, man. in cash. - - right now!
不是X的}
This is not about money.
是嗬之
This is about power!
@里有新老大
There's a new king in the streets.
@是o你和你的手下提醒
This is a message he has for your people.
-你的r代^去了  -死的v史  普托
- You are history. - Fucking history, goddamn puto.
你他在干什么
What the fuck are you doing now, man?
你了
You're crazy!
金・威利f
King willie says...
我不H能⑺滥愕娜怏w
..not only do I have to kill you,...
能ё吣愕撵`魂
..but I have to take your soul.
伏都教的咒Z
Voodoo magic.
死的伏都教
Fucking voodoo magic, man.
但你知道  我砀嬖V你我的信仰
But you know what? I tell you what I believe.
好蛏涎
Shit happens.
快_
Shoot it!
混蛋
Fucker!
好蛏涎
Sh... shit happens.
Shit happens.
我F在在圣佩德_的e墅^外
I'm standing just outside a penthouse complex in san pedro...
有20人死亡
..involving as many as 20 people.
死者身份不明
it's uncertain who they were.
有蟾嬷赋
One report indicates
也S是恐怖的牙I加伏都教徒
It might be the feared jamaican voodoo posse.
我去做身wz查  我的t生f
I go in for my physical and the doctor says
"我需要精子  大便和尿"
"i need a semen,Stool and urine sample."
我f"t生  我很忙
I say "gee, doc, I'm in a big hurry.
我能不能只把妊留下"
can I just leave my underwear?"
上帝啊
Oh, god.
有消息Q
Word is
里面至少有50具尸w
there may be as many as 50 more dead bodies up there.
看那  是波普
Oh, man, it's pope.
那寄生x肯定住在上
That parasite must live in his car.
我硖理  公共P系我最拿手了
I'll handle it. pr's my specialty.
他f你e沾手@案子
Word is they want your ass off the job.
-托尼  伙  -你是l
- tony, my man! - who the hell are you?
我是你最忠的粉z  每次都看你的演出
Your biggest fan! catch your show all the time.
-我有工作要做  -你要做的就是Lhc
- I got a job to do! - Your job is to root garbage for elsewhere.
-M去^了?  -是的  我r正要M去
- been inside? - Yeah. we were gonna go in with our guys,...
但是接到o通知f
But we were told on a radio
不管l生什么  任何人都不能M去
Transmission nobody goes in under any circumstances.
所有挝蛔⒁  邦{查T⒔邮终{查
All units, be advised. federal offcers will handle investigation.
-我什么都]到  走  -你是老大
- we didn't hear that. let's go. - you're the boss.
x・泰在F槟蟮...
This is cheryl tyer reporting live...
@手筒真不e  介意我借用一下
Hey, nice flashlight. mind if I borrow it?
死
Damn!
很眼熟
Look familiar?
操
Fuck.
老天
Oh, god.
雷蒙・S嘉  那大毒n
Ramon vega, the crack king.
是|洛杉最大的子  每周u出100公斤
Biggest operator in east LA. 100 kils a week.
槭裁此]被皮  @些混蛋是什么人
Why isn't he skinned? and who are they assholes?
是牙I加人
they are jamaicans.
金・威利的手下
King willie's boys.
@毫o意x
That makes no sense.
是伏都教x式  我^  他挖出他的心
This was a voodoo ritual. I've seen it before. they took his heart out.
-榱耸裁  -都是人的方法
- what for? - Terror tactics, man.
榱税橙得屁L尿流
You know, to scare the shit out of their enemies.
-金・威利  -l是死的金・威利
- king willie. - who the hell is king willie?
金・威利  伏都教洛杉分教的神父
King willie, voodoo priest of the LA posses.
在他的萘ψ得大前
Ran the terror gangs for Edward seaga in Jamaica...
鄣氯A・西嘉在牙I加\I恐怖M
..till he got too powerful.
]他允S  牙I加的^^都不敢有所行
The Jamaican chiefs won't make a move without his approval.
他的到底l生了什么
So what the fuck happened?
死!
Shit!
@里有幸存者
Hey, we got a survivor!
她在f什么
What's she saying?
不知道  不清她在f什么
I don't know. she's not making any sense.
她一直在f"耗碚宜了"
She keeps saying "ei diablo vino por ellos." the devil came for them.
如果@是那些哥比人干的
If it's the colombians did this,
槭裁此不管吊著的老大和裸w的女友
Why'd they leave their boss hanging and his girl naked on the floor?
-@不是哥比人干的  -y道是火斓娜?
- It wasn't the colombians. - Our friend from the armoury?
是的
Right.
我有新的κ至
We got a new player in town.
^  ~克  看看@
Come over here, mike. check this out.
那是什么
What is that?
看起硐衩^或是什么的
Looks like a spear tip or something.
@里是禁^
This is a restricted area.
我希望你R上消失
I want it cleared immediately.
你正站在C上面
You're walking on physical evidence.
-我碚疹她  -我  你退后
- We'll take care of her. - She's with me.Just back off!
中尉  我想为跟你
Lieutenant, I'd like a word with you in private, please.
他f猿植恍甘悄阕畲蟮c
They say that persistence is what your most outstanding quality.
-我知道@事w你管...  -你]我f
- I know this is your show... - you're not listening to me!
你太多管e事  而且你干涉了太多我的工作
You got a big nose and you're sticking it too far in my business.
你好了  下次如果你再越界
Maybe you can hear this. the next time you cross me,...
-你永h消失
- ..you're gonna turn up missing.
-w博  快把那z影s出去
- Garber, the man with the camera.Get him.Right now!
是  L官
Yes, sir.
-快c走_  -站上c
- All right. Come on.let's go. - Stay away.
-我操  把我的z像Co我  -o我]嘴
- Hey, fuck you, man! give me my camera! - Shut the fuck up.
等等  我有嘣谶@  我是一名者
Hey, wait a minute! I got my rights! I'm a journalist.
-哈里根  -]嘴  快走
- harrigan! harrigan! - shut up. let's go.
你想掩些什么  媒w有嘀道
Smells like a cover-up. the press has a right to know!
把他С龃  搜他的身
Take him out of the building. search him.
你也o我L出去
Now you get the hell out of here.
你是哪根[  P斯
Who the hell are you, keyes?
是@世界上你唯一不想惹的人
The last person in the world you wanna fuck with.
想我槟泸傲  孩子
Wanna make me proud, kid?
M你所能  跟住他  查出他她去哪
Take your bag of tricks, stay with them, find out where they take her.
稍后在洛杉塔酒吧
Meet me later at la cita's.
小心  @些家伙不好惹
And be careful. these guys are good.
不用心  O是我的特L
Hey, don't worry! surveillance is my specialty.
很好  _始行影
Ok, then. just get going.
找到他  行b
Go get 'em, lone ranger.
丹尼  著  我要好好理@件事
Danny, look here. we gotta take this real cool.
@些家伙m然不是毒品管制局的人
These guys sure aren't the dea
但仍是P斯的手下
But it's still keyes's party.
你呆在@  不要被lF了  我一c硪你
You stick around, stay out of sight. I'll meet you at one o'clock.
我再好好搜查一下那房g  如何?  等我
We'll take a good look at that room, ok? hey, wait for me.
丹尼  不要逞英雄  明白?
Danny boy, no hero stuff, understand?
丹丹  小丹尼
Dan-dan-dannyboy.
小心c  丹尼
Watch your ass, danny boy.
她]有去t院
She never made it.
邦{查T就在那等著
The feds were waiting.
直接把她d上了直升wC
Hustled her off in a chopper.
-我猜猜  那架y色云雀式直升C?  -就是那架
- let me guess. a silver alouette? - that very one.
知道  你的老朋友P斯
And guess what. your pal keyes was running the whole show.
跟他的愚蠢的跟班  操v著整^程
And his butt boys.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
你做得非常出色  小伙子
You done real good, kid.
明天  _始跟P斯
Now tomorrow, start a tail on keyes.
注意他的一e一
Everything he does, every where he goes.
你交上好\的
Who knows? you might just get lucky.
中尉
Lieutenant!
交好\
Luck...
...是我的特L
...is my specialty.
我深信不疑
Yeah. I bet it is.
不好意思  失陪一下  中尉
Now, if you'll excuse me, lieutenant,
我有一些重要的工作要做
I got some serious police work to attend to.
小妞我砹
Come to papa.
-你的蛋蛋好吧了?  -很好
- Hey, are your balls ok? - Fine.
你的呢
How are yours?
-不好意思  她是我妹妹  -什么
- Hey, do you mind? it's my sister. - Say what?
其你不是
Oh, you're not my sister,aren't you.
混蛋  你到底在找l  P斯
Son of a bitch. who are you really chasing, keyes?
_工了
Time to go to work.
-死的  -丹尼
- Shit.  - Dannyboy.
~克
Mike?
老天
Oh, god!
不  不  上帝啊!
No. no. oh, god!
圣母利
oh, mother of god!
求你e⑽
please, no!
...有暴力A向  迫型人格
...violence prone, obsessive/compulsive personality,
T用武力
...a history of excessive physical force...
...做了18年的洛杉警察
...throughout his 18 years as a los angeles police offcer.
11v警和1v公共汽的p
Also responsible for the destruction
有著不可推卸的任
of 11 patrol cars, a citybus...
那你又怎么看他在警局期g
What about ten commendations for valour...
多_10次的嘉
What about ten commendations for valour
以及移浦匕傅挠
and the best felony arrest record in the history of this department?
因槲业母深A
That and my intervention on your behalf
你才能保住你的跫帽
Are the only reasons you still have a job.
但是如果局L知道的
If it were up to the chief,
他就丹尼的死起V你并停你的
He'd charge you with detective archuleta's death and suspend you.
事上  他把@件事交o了我理
As it is, he left it in my hands.
F在  @No政策
Now,This John wayne attitude
一意孤行作L⒉痛嬖
flagrant disregard for policy is gonna end now.
在我的指]下
No one under my command will
]有人能阻止@次由P斯IУ
impede the progress of this federal task force
邦{查行
headed by agent Keyes.
]有人
No one.
就@
That's it.
散
Dismissed.
~克  你管得太多了  放手吧
Mike, you're too close to this. stay out of it.
@是警察的事  他不能警察局撒手不管
It's a police matter. they can't keep the department out of it.
我找到⒑Φつ岬娜说
We'll find Danny's killer.
L  我和丹尼一起在街^
Captain, Danny and I came up together.
巡了15年
15 years on the fucking street!
不管l⒘说つ  我都他血血
Whoever killed him's gonna pay. I'm gonna finish it.
D什么呀
Hey, come on. what is this?
好了  混蛋
Listen, shithead.
我不管你要δ混蛋怎么
I don't give a fuck what you want with
因楝F在@是我的私事
this asshole because now it's personal.
他死定了
And he's a dead man.
你F在的行槌出了你的嘞  我警告你
What you're dealing with is over your head. I'm warning you...
你根本不知道你在干什么
You! you don't know what you're dealing with.
是我警告你  e他踔我的路
And I'm warning you. stay the fuck out of my way!
-我硎帐八  -不
- I'll take care of him. - No.
由他去
Let him go.
我快得手了
We're too close.
\如所f
Claiming as his
牙I加和哥比毒n掌握著真相
turf controlled by the jamaican and colombian drug lords.
^m看我接下淼蟮
Watch as we continue our report.
洛杉已唾手可得
LA is up for grabs,...
@座曾美好的城市⒙淙肽切
the spoils of our once fine city going to the ruthless scum...
肆意制造屠⒑土餮事件的人渣手中
who can spread the most carnage and blood in our streets.
五混蛋人渣和一名秀的警察
five assorted trash and one good cop
警局中最秀的一T
one of the best on our force.
l⑹窍乱受害者  而市L又在哪
Who's next? where's the mayor?
他甚至根本就不在洛杉...
He's not even in the city...
忘了他吧  都Y束了
Forget it. it's over.
~克  死  知道  @不是你一人的鸲
Mike, god damn it. this ain't your personal little war, you know.
我也鄣つ
I loved Danny, too.
你告V我只有F作鸩拍艽婊
Hey, you told me the only way you survive is because you're a team.
凡事都有擅  得
The door swings both ways. remember?
好吧  我并肩作
All right. we'll do it together.
告V我一些P于P斯的情r
Come on. talk to me about keyes.
^去三天我一直在跟他
we've been on him for the last three days.
他根本就]有找毒子
and they're not looking for drug dealers.
而是在全市^安b那些奇怪的雷_探y器
Yeah. they've been setting up weird radar sensors all over downtown.
我用M了一切k法去跟著他
I used my whole repertory to keep up with them!
我L用探y器呙杷
I had scanners on them,
但是被他察X了
but they scrambled my shit up.
他的O涮先M  我根本o法靠近
They had equipment I can't begin to touch.
今天早晨...
And then this morning...
我把他跟G了  -我把他跟G了
- l lost 'em. - We lost them.
-在哪跟G的?  - 弗r街和工I街街口
- Lost where? - vernon and lndustry.
-他就像人g蒸l了一  -在屠宰^?
-I mean they like fucking disappeared! - the slaughterhouse district?
是的  @大崽  我是f  岬媚烤了
Yeah, and in this heat, whoo! I mean, bo and barbecue!
不管P斯在找什么  他已找到了  或即⒄业
so whatever keyes is looking for, he's found it, or damn close to it.
利昂娜  我想金・威利
Leona, I want to meet with king willie.
看砦液屯利有著相同的麻
Willie and I seem to have the same problem.
-而你  跟我一起走  -~克  @o法k到
- In the meantime, you come with me. - Mike, it's impossible!
就@么Q定了
Just do it.
死!
Fuck!
W米加一  @里是控制中心
Omega 1. this is control.
@里是W米加一
This is omega 1.
我只有二十二分安全作Irg
We only have 22 minutes on safe window of operation.
-是  L官  -最后一次z查byb置
- Yes, sir. - Verify that final telemetry check.
_始y
Start your test now.
跟呙  三  二  一
Scan track three, two, one,
_始
Mark.
六  紫外的正常
Number six, power up on the uv banks.
紫外已完成  浜媒邮y
We're complete on the lower uv banks. ready for testing.
第二步  z查周的囟茸化
Second level, check for ambient temperature variations.
你有煞昼rg  F在_始
You got two minutes. now get going.
所有挝
To all units.
所有挝  你有大s20分rg完成任
All units, you have approximately 20 minutes to finish your task.
-收到  -增加@紫外
- Roger. - Increase this uv.
上升到42%
Up 42 per cent.
你朋友死于利器刺入胸腔
Your friend died as the result of an intrusion in the chest cavity
@差c把他的心撕成砂
..by an edged weapon that nearly cleaved the heart in two.
死亡是瞬gl生的
Death was instantaneous.
他全身的骨^都被去掉了  我奈匆^
He was boned like a fish. I've never seen anything like this.
e碰任何|西
Please, do not touch anything.
t生  其他那些受害者的情r怎么
Doctor, what about the other victims?
有什么e的lF
Anything there?
邦{查M砹怂自己的法t
The federal team brought in their own forensic examiners.
我是@城市的尸T和首席病理W家
I am the medical examiner and the chief pathologist in the city,
但是他就@么把我完全了
and they've cut me out completely.
不管怎  你能看到他收集到的C吧
Anyway you can get a look at evidence the feds have collected?
-我是f  他肯定做^  -@很困y
- I mean, they must have run tests. - It won't be easy.
t生
Doctor,
@是我牡つ岬氖掷镎业降
l pried this from danny's hands.
正是它把丹尼引上了屋
this is what took him into the rafters.
-@缀]有重量  -但它s像F一愉h利
- It has almost no weight. - But it cuts like steel.
我砜纯
Let me see.
F在我把它放大十五f倍
We are now at 150,000 times normal magnification.
真令人@
Astonishing.
@N元素根本不存在于元素周期表上
This material doesn't correspond to anything on the periodic table.
-中尉  那到底是什么  -我不知道
- lieutenant, what the hell is that thing?  - I don't know.
但肯定不是五金店里I的
It's not from a hardware store.
-不是用的  -很好的假O
- No military?  - Uh, good guess.
不是他G的  就是他想找的
Either something that got away, or something they want.
P斯  我已x真相很近了
Keyes. ah, we're getting closer now to what happened
住手
Hey, no!
放松  小伙子  把你的收起
Easy, kid. put your gun away.
金・威利要你
King willie will see you now.
-]事  -你不想我跟你一起去
- It's ok. - Don't you want me with you?
稍后我打o你
I'll call you later.
-你想我跟著你  -稍后我打o你
- You want me to follow you? -I'll call you later!
整c大麻怎么
You want some ganja, man?
牌
License plate number.
1-8-8
不不不  1-8-8-3
No, no. 1-8-8-3
死!
Oh, fuck!
去你的"凡事都有擅"
The door swings both ways, my ass.
@事阂灿擅
This door swings both ways.
xxd我一程
Thanks for the ride.
你
You know,
在少抽c
you guys really ought to cut down.
他f你想跟我聊聊
They say you want to talk to me.
他f你在暗中椭我
They say you're offering me favours.
告V我你@么做的原因  死警察
Tell me why, babylon.
警察先生
Mr policeman.
-我需要一些情  -情?
-I want some information. - information.
P于那⑹
About the one that's doing all the killing?
他先⒘四愕娜
He killed your people.
F在又⑽业
Now mine.
我想你知道他是l
I think you know who he is.
我想要找到他
I want him.
我不知道他是l
I don't know who he is.
但我知道他在哪
But I know where he is.
-在另外一世界  -你在胡f些什么
- The other side. - What are you talking about?
在`界中
The spirit world, man.
看到
You see,
是@拥
it's always the same.
淼倪是要
There's no stopping what can't be stopped.
死的是要死
No killing what can't be killed.
e故弄玄了
Hey, make sense, man.
⒘四愀我的手下的那|西
This thing that's killing your people and mine
碜粤硗庖世界
is from the other side.
我能感受到他的存在
I can feel him all around.
但除非他碚夷
You can't see the eyes of the demon...
不然就o法用肉眼看到他
until him come calling.
@真是恐怖
This is dread, man.
非常恐怖
Truly dread.
@里]你的事了  警察先生
Nothing else for you here, policeman.
走吧
Time to go.
r刻做好
Prepare yourself.
"他的基地在圣山之上"
"his foundation lie in the holy mountain."
"西拉"
"selah."
@里是托尼・普波在充M恐值
This is tony pope live from la,
洛杉城槟直播
the city of fear.
那B的⑹诌在^m著他每天的屠
The psycho-vigilante killer continues his daily diet for murder.
高斓氖w
Bodies strung out,
被皮的尸w  以及氖w中挖出的心K
bodies with the skins ripped off, the hearts torn from the cadavers.
而就在才  金・威利  那毒n
And just recently, king willie, the drug lord,...
那f旱亩n  在一l小巷的D角被⒘
the vicious drug lord found in an alley just around the corner...
他的^被砍了下  而脊椎t被拆散了
with his head cut off and his spinal column torn from the body.
真是死有余辜
A fitting demise to the prince of powder.
先是丹尼  接著是金・威利  而你恰好都在
First danny, then king willie. and you were right there!
他在耍你呢  你得小心c
He's playing with you, mike. you've gotta be careful.
好的  我都要小心  P斯那怎么
Yeah. we all gotta be careful. what about keyes?
-有新lF  -P斯@有c棘手
- Anything there? - Definitely something slippery about keyes.
全名叫彼得・J・P斯
Seems there's a peter j keyes.
@得了是康奈大W的物理W博士W位
Phd physical sciences, cornell.
以的成I并加入鹇苑烙研究所
Hot out of college and into the strategic defense lnstitute.
赡旰
Then two years later
被任命榭哲情蟛块T的上尉
commissioned as a captain in air force lntelligence.
~克  我查不下去了  超^我范了
Mike, this is a dead end. we're way out of our league!
著  我不管他有多大的眍^
Look, I don't care how big this is and who's involved.
他⒘说つ  他必付出代r
This guy killed danny and he's going to fall!
-t生那怎么  -我在@  中尉
- Now whatabout the good doctor? - Yeah, I'm here, lieutenant.
邦局清除了所有C
The federal authorities erased everything from the computer file
除了
except for this
e墅的木碎片的部分化Y果
Part of a chemical test on a fragment of wood from the penthouse.
它含有微量的牛血
And it contained traces...
和大量的固醇
..of cattle blood and heavy traces of steroids.
我J⑺赖つ岬词
I believe whoever killed detective
最近曾到^屠宰
Had recently been in a slaughterhouse.
屠宰  正是我第一次跟GP斯的地方
Slaughterhouse.That's where llostkeyes the first time!
恩  我在那找到他的
Yeah. that's where we'll find him.
坐地F^  一小r后伯恩斯站
Take the metro. I'll pick you up at Burns station in an hour.
你]看到P斯的人  不代表他不在附近
Justbecause you don't see keyes's boys doesn't mean they're notaround.
乖乖的在里坐著
I just want you to stay in the car. ok?
你和我R上  坐好ey跑
Your mom and I won't be very long. you sit still.
我很快就回
We'll be back in a few minutes.
明白了
All right?
-走吧  H鄣  -恩
- Come on, honey. - Yes.
-走哪  -倪@^去
- which way was it? - Down here.
受死吧  你@只]皮狗
Take that, you scum-sucking dog.
要吃糖
Want some candy?
布恩  布恩
Brian? brian!
-你立刻o我回  -咪 我看到鬼了
- You come here right this minute! - Mommy, I saw a ghost.
要吃糖  要吃糖
Wantsome candy? wantsome candy?
安息吧
Rest.
要吃糖
Wantsome candy?
丹尼的
Danny's necklace.
我在繁忙r段坐地F
I hate the subway at rush hour.
@r段空位很y找  如果你有幸找到了
It's hard enough to find a seat, and if you do,
上面要么是有尿的  要么是有屎的
Someone's pissed in it or thrown up over it.
崴牢伊
This damn heat is killing me, man.
嘿  我上了
Hey, it's me!
-我很上R啊  -臭美
- I look great! - Oh, shit.
]有名  大叔
No autographs, pop.
-看  那河空位  -e碰我
- Look. there's two seats right there. - Don't touch me!
L_
Hey! get off!
麻┦抡娑
This shit never ends.
-你戆  -混蛋
- After you. - Asshole!
-_一下 警察k事  -e趼
- Excuse me. police business. - Get out of my way!
嘿    H我一下  砺
Hey, baby. besame mucho. come on!
你看上去挺有同情心的嘛
You look like a sympathetic dude.
我的兄弟最近要做cIu
My, uh... partner here needs an operation .
但我手^有co  你明白我意思吧
But we're a little short of cash, if you know what I mean?
不需要那
No need for that.
恩  X啊
Mm, money.
L_
get the hell away from me!
不要逼我  我真的_的
I know how to use this thing! don't make me use this thing!
我敢打我的比你的大
Bet mine's bigger than yours!
我砀愣ㄋ
I'll take that.
-住手  警察  -@次麻┐罅
- Hold it. police! - We're in trouble now.
-所有人都不S  -警察  不S
- Nobody move! - Alto, policia, no se muevan!
大家深呼吸  eo
Everybody take a deep breath, loosen your sphincters.
e逞一r之勇
We don't need any rush-hour rambos there.
把放下  混球
Tu tambien, motherfucking baby!
放下  然后坐下 坐下
Drop it and sit down! sientate!
的那是什么
What the hell is that?
利昂娜  你好吧
leona, you ok?
它在里  С丝x_
This is it! he's in the train! get these people out of here!
-吉瑞  -l生什么事  -趴下  趴下
- Jerry! - What's happening? - Get down! get down!
快x_
Get out of the way!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜
Leona!
利昂娜  他走  走啊
Leona, get 'em out! go! go!
快
Now!
吉瑞
Jerry!
利昂娜  快走啊
Leona, do it!
快
Now!
我在@里
Hey! over here!
α  ^戆
Yeah, that's right. come and get it.
快c  走啊  走啊
Come on! move it! move it!
走快c  走
Let's go! vamos!
走
move it!
e慌  走就可以了  走  快走
Don't panic, just go! go! vamos!
天哪  你是什么|西啊
Jesus christ. what the fuck are you?
等一下
Wait!
走啊  走啊  快c
Vamos!vamos! come on!
向前走啊  快  你  走啊
Keep walking! come on, you too! vamonos!
戆  狗娘B的
Come on, motherfucker!
要吃糖
Wantsome candy?
我跳舞吧
Let's dance!
快_
Come on, get out of the way!
_
Get out of the way!
快  出  出
Come on, out! out! out!
快c  跑
Come on, move it!
去那  去有光的地方
That way! that way! towards the light! the light!
快  都出
Come on! get out!
快c啊
Come on.
走
Vamos!
天哪
Oh, god.
吉瑞
Jerry.
上帝  怎么又⑷肆
God, not again.
快x_  e踔
Ok, move your ass! move out the way!
-l生了什么事  -他的真是一鐾  中尉
- Watch out! what's happening? - it's a fucking slaughter, lieutenant.
天啊
Oh, god!
吉瑞
Hey, jerry!
利昂娜
Oh, leona! leona!
醒醒  利昂娜
Oh, please. leona... oh.
-她怎恿  -活著  但^度@
- how's she doing? - deep shock, but she's alive.
我到胎旱男奶  她言辛
I hear foetal heart sounds. she's pregnant.
立刻送到洛杉t治
Let's move. la county. stat!
_c
Stand back.
等下  一  二  三  起
On three. one, two, three. load up.
_
Out of my way!
_  快走_
Move out the way! move it! move it!
等一下  我看看
Uh, wait a minute. let me see.
-吉瑞在哪  -我不知道
- Where's jerry? - I don't know.
我找到了他的警章
We found his badge.
哪些人受了
Who got hit this time?
五小混混
Five gang members,...
一些乘客
..bunch of commuters.
@f不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
他都有
They were all armed.
-什么意思  -指]官的
- What do you mean? - It's the chief.
在@等著  喂
Wait here. yeah?
-那情r怎么了  -他的很糟
- What the hell's going on down there? - It's a damn nightmare.
@次遇害的都是平民
Civilians this time.
-全都死了  -是  和之前的一
- Allkilled? - Yeah. just like the others.
的
Damn!
吉瑞
Jerry!
活鬼  他的l生了什么事
Holy shit! what the hell is going on here?
伙  打_z像C  快_z像C
Hey, guys, get the camera on! get the camera on this right now!
拍下@些事
Get that goddamn thing on film!
l生了什么事
What's going on?
哈里根
Hey, harrigan!
@次受害人更多  pЦ乐
More victims! more mutilations!
-去死吧  -普波
- Fuck you! - Pope!
普波  你在  普波  l生了什么事
Pope? are you there, pope? pope, what's going on?
L官  那警察又砹
Sir, the cop is back.
的
Goddamn.
哈里根  你就不能省c毫
Harrigan! don't you show up in the damnedest places.
^  中尉  我有些你感d趣的|西
Come here, lieutenant. I got something you might find interesting.
@里是怎么回事
What is this?
我要跟你f多少遍
How many times do I have to tell you?
你不知道你的κ质鞘裁
You don't know what you're dealing with.
@就是你要找的词  很妙吧
There's your killer. wonderful, isn't it?
他的身|散l出信息素  即馕斗肿
Pheromone signature left by his body. scent molecules.
打_三O器
Punch up three.
十年前  一只同N的形在中美洲
Ten years ago one of his kind eliminated an
摧Я艘恢特N精英部
Elite special forces crew in central america.
只有幸存者
There were two survivors.
他f  @N生物一旦被捕
They indicated that, when trapped,
就右环N自С淌
The creature activated a self-destruct device...
威力足以摧三百街^那么大的雨林
..that destroyed enough rainforest to cover 300 city blocks.
完美的武器
Remarkable weaponry.
]e  中尉  他是外星生物
That's right, lieutenant. other-world life forms.
什么
Huh?
一只他的形
A fucking alien!
硫磺u  柬埔寨  特  l出崮芎鸵起矛盾
Iwo jima, cambodia, beirut. drawn by heat and conflict.
他在M行著狩C游  {子  老虎  熊
He's on safari. lions. the tigers. the bears.
我的天
Oh, my!
品  那是一鲇  Π  P斯
Trophies. that's the game, isn't it, keyes?
你就是{子
You're the lion.
@里是它的擦
This is his jungle.
-那槭裁次看不到它
- So why can't we see him?
因樗有超的自lm系y
defensive adaptations are astounding.
它能曲光  完美的窝bg
It's somehow able to bend light. perfect camouflage.
-你欣p@只怪物  -不是它的所作所
- you admire the son of a bitch. - not what he does.
而是它本身的造
For what he is.
有它能Ыo我的|西
For what he can give us.
@是科技的一新r代
A new era of scientific technology.
我一生都在等@C  我不它白白溜走
I've waited a lifetime for this, and I'm not going to miss the chance.
信息素雷_呙xlF它了
We have something on the pheromone scanners.
目嗽谖蓓上
Target one is on the roof.
我花了芍艿rg摸清了它的T
- it's taken us two weeks to learn his patterns.
它每隔商炀磉@里_餐一次
He comes here every two days to feed.
-看硭很喜g牛肉  -我]X得是素食者
- seems he has a taste for beef. - I didn't think he was vegetarian.
我檫@只食肉F淞艘陷阱
Well, we've prepared a trap for this predator.
我肯定@N生物只能用一N光V看物w
We are certain that this being can see in only one spectrum of light -
- t外  -t外?
- infrared. - infrared?
-它靠感崃坎妒  -隔^了崃  它就是瞎子
- He hunts by seeing our heat. - block the heat and he's blind.
@衣服能隔^身w的崃  使它看不到我
These suits insulate body heat, making the team invisible to the creature.
我在地面上覆w了一臃派湫苑勰
We've flooded the place with radioactive dust...
并在每一角落都安b上紫外光
..and installed powerful ultraviolet lighting everywhere.
@N粉末粘附在它身上就使它F形
The dust adheres to his body, making him visible.
液氮 你不是要⑺而是要冰鏊
Liquid nitrogen. you're not gonna kill him. you're gonna freeze him.
-我要生擒它  -它在移恿
- We have to capture him. - He's moving.
K于砹
Finally.
找位子  好好看表演吧
Grab a seat. enjoy the show.
@是v史性的r刻
This is history.
我的目耸巧擒并隔x它
Capture and isolation is our objective.
只有在我下令的r候才能防l
Defensive action only on my orders.
_  行
Power up. lights on. let's get him!
我已M入
We're in.
切Q到紫外
Switch to ultraviolet.
-停止通  -打_A到J^的紫外
- Radio silence. out. - engage ultraviolet units a through j.
-@些干_信是什么  -正在{整  L官
- What's all this interference? - Correcting the problem, sir.
他正在走向二^
They're moving to the second level.
目巳栽诔二翘菥移
Target's still moving, heading towards the number two stairwell.
它正在往陷阱里@
Playing right into it.
等一下
Wait a minute.
它停住了
It's stopped.
它退到了
It's moving back against the wall.
它正往回走  x他越碓竭h了
It's backing up. it's moving away from them.
你的人被耍了
Your boys have been made.
L官  它F在在他周兜圈
Sir, it's circling around behind them.
他出  他掉M陷阱里了
Get 'em out! they're walking into a trap!
P斯  它在三  就在你后面
Keyes, he's behind you. third floor structure. right there!
l在那里嗦  不释ㄓ
Who is this? clear the line.
它看得那死的光  把他P掉  P掉
He sees the damn lights. turn 'em off! turn 'em off! shit!
制止他
Stop him!
-把T打_  -你去死吧
- Door. open it. - Go fuck yourself.
好啊  好
Ok. ok.
_T
The door.
-好的  我_  -你知道你在做什么
- Yes, sir. - You don't know what you're doing.
_了
It's open.
-你把所有|西搞砸的  -去死吧
- You'll ruin everything!  - Fuck yourself!
防l形一  液氮P]
Defensive formation one. nitrogen guns, safeties off.
大家跟著我
Everyone else, follow me .
它就在@里
This is it.
它正向你移  右
He's moving down to your position, right.
w博  它在哪  我看不到它
Garber, where is he? I can't see him.
它就在那里  它就在那里
He's right there! he's right there!
的  它在哪  告V我它的坐
Goddamn it! where is he? well, give me a coordinate! where is he?
-小心  -天哪
- Watch out! - My god.
小心你的
Watch your crossfire!
的
damn
我的防o衣漏饬
I'm losing my pressure.
P斯  你怎恿
Keyes, you all right?
P斯  它在@里
Keyes, it's overhere!
快  的
Come on! damn it.push over!
的  我什么都看不到
Shit! I can't see!
通都中嗔
They're gone.
他全死了
They're all dead.
你想⑽  我就在@
You want me? here lam!
你真是一只
You are one...
丑陋的
..ugly mother...
混蛋
Motherfucker!
猜猜l回砝  你回不了家啦
Guess who's back. Too late to go home now.
快x_@里  哈里根  我砭饶
Get out of here, harrigan. I'm gonna save your ass.
@是我和他之g的鸲
This is between me and him!
天哪...
God...
原硎区B
Birds.
死的B
Damn birds.
好吧  包
Ok, pussyface
邮职
It's your move.
好蛏涎
Shit happens.
啊  天哪
Oh, god. oh, god.
我F在需要像B一
That's all I need is birds.
你行的
You can do it.
我可以做到的  我行的
I can do it. I can do it.
就像渖匣下砟
It's like falling off a log.
的  三十歉叩
Like a 30-storey log. damn!
我可能很好\地到_
Maybe I'll get lucky and fall.
的
Damn it.
伯加利  在普洛斯嫁o王以后
..berengaria, who never set foot in england, was its queen for eightyears...
了八十年的皇后  s奈刺ぷ阌
..aftermarrying this king on cyprus.
-晚安  -赫伯  赫伯  醒醒  有人在我家浴室
- goodluck.- herb? - herb, wake up! there's somebody in the bathroom.
赫伯
Herb!
-e怕  我是警察  -我不J樗怕你
- It's all right. I'm a cop. - I don't think he gives a shit.
的
Shit!
快回屋里去
Get back inside!
的  又要往下滑
Holy moses. not again. shit!
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
槭裁催@只怪物不呆在地面上啊
Why can't this guy stay on the ground?
^  ^
Come on, come on. come on, come on!
^磉@里
Come to papa.
停  把梯停住
Stop! stop the elevator!
停啊
Stop it!
@是什么鬼地方啊
Now where the hell am l?
你在哪
Where are you?
上帝啊
Jesus christ.
@就α  混蛋
That's right, asshole!
好蛏涎
Shit happens!
好  l接著
Ok. who's next?
拿去
Take... it.
1715年
"1715."
哈里根  那里他的l生了什么事
Harrigan! what the fuck happened in there, huh?
活鬼  我差c就成功了
Goddamn it. we came so close!
e心  混球  你有C的
Don't worry, asshole. you'll get another chance.